Welcome to the Cascades. I'm Dina Latimer,
and it would be my pleasure to give you a tour of our quaint and home-like
assisted living community
at the Cascades, which is tucked away.
In a country-like setting in the town of Bethel,
you will receive an unparalleled level of service and amenities that provide a
sense of personal security and peace of mind,
allowing you to feel an immediate sense of belonging.
Our community consists of 42 studios,
one bedroom and two bedroom apartments.
Each apartment has a modern kitchenette, a handicap accessible bathroom,
and individual temperature controlled heating and air conditioning.
In addition to the private space of your apartment,
there's an array of common areas where you can enjoy meals and activities at
your leisure. In our dining room,
you will experience gourmet restaurant style dining with three meals a
day.
You can also sit back and relax in our pub for snacks throughout the day.
We offer exercise classes in a modern private gym setting,
as well as relaxation therapies, daily social activities,
and spiritual programs designed to increase vitality and
maximize an independent lifestyle.
Our care team works closely with each resident to structure their individual
supportive care needs.
Under the guidance of National Healthcare Associates.
We take great pride in our mission to provide kindness,
compassion, service,
and excellence to every one of our residents.
We are committed to creating an exceptional experience and would love
to have you call the Cascades your home.